双峰
第三季第十六集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     TheWalkingNerd  詹木头
翻译     苏小黛  桃小兔  小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     没有影子  Jenny
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
好吧
Okay.
我们到了
So we're here.
然后呢
What now?
集中精力
Pay attention.
一会就知道了
You'll find out.
我在找一个地方
I'm looking for a place.
你明白什么叫地方吗
Do you understand the place?
地方
Place?
有三个人分别给了我那地方的坐标
Three people have given me coordinates to that place.
其中两份是吻合的
Two of the coordinates match.
你会怎么做  理查德
What would you do, Richard?
我会去查那处两份吻合的
I'd check out the two that match.
你真是个聪明的年轻人
You're a very bright young man.
我们就快到达吻合的那个地方了
And we're very close to the two that match.
这显示就在那上面
It says it's right up there.
我们要上去吗
We're going up there?
是的
Yeah.
我们现在就上去
We're going up there right now.
是人
People?
天啊
Dear God.
就是这里吗
Is this it?
我打赌就在那岩石上
I'll bet it's right up there on that rock.
我比你老25岁
I'm 25 years your senior.
拿着这个  上去
Take this and get on up there.
如果接近了就会发出嘀嘀声
It'll beep when you're close
如果到了地方就会持续作响
And make a continuous tone when you're on it.
告诉我你发现了什么
Let me know what you find.
我到了
I'm there!
永别了  我的孩子
Good-bye, my son.
破望远镜
Bad, bad binoculars.
Bad binoculars!
破破破  真是破望远镜
Bad, bad, bad binoculars!
全部
发送失败
你今早听到那鸟叫了吗
You hear that bird this morning?
当然
Sure as shit did.
谁来了
Who's this here?
他们来干什么
What the hell are they doing here?
看起来没人在
Well, it looks like nobody's home.
你怎么推断出来的呢  神探夏洛克
And how did you deduce that, sherlock?
威尔森  混蛋  去找辆车停在什么地方
Wilson, you son of a bitch, go grab a car and park somewhere
别让人看到  盯着这房子
Over there out of sight and stake out this house.
好吧
Okay.
过来
Come here.
我要查查这地方
I'm gonna check out the place of business--
幸运7号的保险
Lucky 7 insurance, hmm?
威尔森
Wilson!
快去
Get going!
赶紧滚蛋
Good riddance.
医生说的跟你说的一样
I just heard what you've been telling me.
他处于昏迷中
He's in a coma,
但主要体征都很正常  也很强健
But his vital signs are good, strong.
是啊  但人们陷入昏迷的话
Yeah, but when people go into a coma,
可以持续很多年
they can stay there for years.
道吉不会的
Oh, Dougie's not gonna do that.
妈妈  昏迷跟电有关吗
Mom, does a coma have something to do with electricity?
没有  亲爱的
No, honey.
他这情况是有关的
Well, in this case, it did.
就...  我说过我来搬了
Well, just-- I told you I'd carry it.
我就是不知道  他在这  他在这
I just don't know--here he is. Here he is.
布什内尔  我们一听到消息就赶来了
Bushnell, we came as soon as we heard.
他们是米彻姆兄弟  珍妮
These are the Mitchum brothers, Janey-E.
道吉的朋友
They're friends of Dougie's.
桑尼·吉姆  他们就是...
Um, Sonny Jim, these are the men who, uh--
给你买游乐设施和车的人
Who bought your gym set and-- and the car.
谢谢你们  谢谢你们  先生
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
-谢谢  -别客气
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
所有小孩都应该有一套  对吗
Every kid should have a gym set, huh?
我看看这个  瞧瞧
Let me see that. Look at that.
我们  我们之前遇到过这种情况
We've-- we've seen this before.
这种事时有发生
Uh, this sort of thing happens,
你不想做饭
and you don't feel like cooking.
也不想吃医院的食物
You don't want to eat hospital food.
但是...
But... oh.
吉米  你必须得吃东西
Jimmy, you've got to eat.
这些就是手指三明治
These are what you call finger sandwiches.
吃吧
Go ahead.
用手指把它拈起来
You pick it up with your fingers.
非常好  所以才叫手指三明治
Very good. That's why they call it a finger sandwich.
姑娘们  去把折叠托盘拿进来
Girls, go--go-- go bring in the, uh-- the folding trays.
或许我们该出去吃一顿
Hey, hey, maybe we should eat outside.
不不不  我们一会儿就走
No, no, no, no, no, we're not gonna stay.
都是给你们的
This is all for you.
我们只想尽所能帮点忙
We just want to be as helpful as possible
还有表达我们的尊敬之情
and, uh--and, uh-- and, uh, pay our respects.
总体来看
All things considered,
他气色不错
he looks good.
是啊  医生都很乐观
Yeah, well, the doctors are very hopeful.
能不能麻烦把你的钥匙给我  琼斯太太
If I can trouble you for a key, Mrs. Jones,
我们还准备给你家送点东西
we're gonna go stock your house, too.
好吧...
Okay, um...
给你  谢谢
Here you go. Thank you.
是因为...
It was...
什么来着
Like, what?
电吗
Electricity?
妈
Mom.
我要尿尿了
I have to go pee.
好吧
Okay.
我们去厕所
Let's go find you the little boys' room.
这位是布什内尔
This is Bushnell.
-我是菲尔·拜斯比  -你好  菲尔
- Uh, Phil Bisby here. Hello, Phil.
刚刚联调局的来过了  要找道吉
The FBI was just here looking for Dougie.
-什么  -联调局
- What? The FBI.
联调局
The FBI?
是的  他们要找道吉
Yeah, they were looking for dougie.
找道吉
Looking for dougie?
是的
Yeah.
他又做了什么  他还在昏迷之中
Wha--what's he done now? He's in a coma.
我...
Uh, I-I-I--
你告诉他们我们在这了吗
Did you tell them we're here?
说了  然后他们就走了
Yeah, I did, and then they left.
-说了吗  -是的
- You did? - Yeah.
他们什么时候走的
When did they leave?
大概十分钟前  先生
About ten minutes ago, sir.
好吧
Okay.
今天有得等了
Looks like it's gonna be a long day.
还记得那个叫萨米的吗
Remember that guy Sammy?
记得
Yeah.
他死了
He passed away.
他是个好人
He was a good guy.
我还欠他钱
I owed him money.
你觉得有点内疚了
You feel bad about that?
这是什么
What is this now?
他们中有道吉吗
Is one of them guys Dougie?
道格拉斯在吗
Douglas?
他们中有人长得和老板一样吗
Do any of them look anything like our boss?
没有  蠢货  道吉不在
No, stupid, none of them is Dougie.
你能专心点吗
Will you settle down now?
这是最后一包了  贱人
It's the last bag, hutch.
这他妈是最后一包了
It's the last fucking bag.
你姨妈来了吗
You on the rag?
来了又怎么样
What if I fucking was?
好吧
Okay.
看上去像个巡游马戏团
Looks like a fucking circus parade.
加长豪华轿车...
Stretch limo...
穿粉色裙子的女人
Girls in pink.
没有道格拉斯·琼斯
No Douglas Jones.
搞什么
What the fuck?
扎瓦斯基会计公司
喂
Hello.
你好
你们占了我的私人车道
You're in my driveway.
我们没在你的私人车道上
We're not in your driveway.
我们连你的私人车道的边都没沾  混蛋
We're not even close to your fucking driveway, asshole.
滚你妈的
Go fuck yourself!
我挪车
I move car.
这个混账
That fucker!
搞什么  香塔尔
What the fuck, Chantal?
那个混球真的气死老娘了
That douchebag is really pissing me off!
香塔尔
Ah, Chantal!
快掩护我
Fucking winged me!
你把所有事都搞砸了
This shit is fucking up the whole thing.
快离开这里
Get us the fuck out of here.
这附近都住着些什么人啊
What the fuck kind of neighborhood is this?
大家压力都很大  布拉德利
People are under a lot of stress, Bradley.
是啊
Yeah.
联调局
FBI!
把枪放下
Put the gun down!
我说了把枪放下
I said put the gun down!
慢慢地远离你的枪
Now slowly back away from your gun.
把枪收起来  好吗
Put down the gun, okay?
我们带姑娘们走  好吗
Let's get the girls and get out of here, all right?
我需要增援和一辆救护车
I need backup and an ambulance
兰斯洛特法院这里
At Lancelot Court.
兰斯洛特法院
Lancelot court!
你
醒了
完全清醒了
One hundred percent.
终于
另一个
他没有
回去
他还在外面
拿上这个
你有种子吗
Do you have the seed?
你拿到种子了吗
你得再帮我做一个
I need you to make another one.
我明白
道吉
Dougie?
爸爸
Dad?
道吉
Dougie.
你好啊  桑尼·吉姆
Hello, Sonny Jim.
我的天...
Oh, my...
道吉
Dougie.
你好  珍妮·E
Hello, Janey-E.
道吉醒了
Dougie's back!
我就知道
I knew it.
珍妮·E  你能去叫个医生来吗
Janey-E, would you please go find a doctor right now?
-好的  -桑尼·吉姆...
- Yeah. - Sonny jim...
你和妈妈一起去吧
Why don't you go with your mom?
好吧
Okay.
布什内尔  把那盘三明治递过来
Bushnell, pass me some of those sandwiches.
我要饿死了
I'm starving.
办公室刚才打电话来
The office just called.
说联调局正在找你
The FBI was there looking for you.
太好了
Perfect.
你可总算是挺过来了
You sure came through this pretty strong.
慢着点  你这是要干什么
Whoa, whoa, what do you think you're doing?
我不用再输液了
I no longer need this IV.
医生  你能不能检查一下我的生命体征
Doctor, will you confirm that my vitals are a-okay?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
布什内尔  帮我拿一下衣服
Bushnell, my clothes, please.
在你后面的橱子里
The cabinet behind you.
道吉  你确定你会没事的吗
Dougie, are you sure this is a good idea?
我没问题的
It's a good idea.
看样子你确实没什么大问题了
It looks like it's a pretty good idea.
我去给你准备出院手续
I'll prep your release papers.
珍妮·E  去把车开到门口来
Janey-E, please bring the car around front.
我穿好衣服就下楼找你们
I'll get dressed and meet you downstairs.
好的  来吧  桑尼·吉姆
Okay. Come on, Sonny Jim.
爸爸让我们去把车开来
Daddy thinks we should get the car around.
谢谢  布什内尔
Thank you, Bushnell.
爸爸的话变多了
Dad sure is talking a lot.
确实是这样  桑尼·吉姆
Yeah, he sure is, Sonny Jim.
布什内尔  给我你左胳膊下面的枪套里
Bushnell, I'm gonna need to borrow the .32 snub nose
那把32口径短管手枪用一下
you wear in the shoulder holster under your left arm.
没问题  道吉
Sure thing, Dougie.
你没事吧
Is everything all right?
我能帮上忙吗
Can I help you in any way?
你可以帮我打电话给米彻姆兄弟
You can get the Mitchum brothers on the phone.
没问题
Sure thing.
他们把私人电话留给我了
They gave me their personal number.
我已经设成了快速拨号
I got it on speed dial.
喂
Hello.
是布拉德吗
Yeah, t-this Brad?
是罗德啊
Oh, Rod.
先别挂电话
Listen, uh, hold on.
道吉要跟你说几句话
Dougie's got to talk to you.
罗德  我二十分钟后带着我的家人到赌场
Rod, I'm bringing my family to the casino in 20 minutes.
在大厅等我们
Meet us in the lobby.
没问题  道吉
Whatever you need, Dougie.
然后我需要坐飞机去华盛顿州的斯波坎
And then I need a plane to Spokane, Washington.
那我们给飞机加满油
We're gassing up the jet.
我们这就把油加满
We're gassing it up right now.
布拉德利  我们要去华盛顿州  斯波坎市
Bradley, we're headed to Spokane, Washington.
二十分钟后大堂见
Meet you in the lobby in 20 minutes.
没问题
You got it.
对  加满油
Yeah. Gas it up.
-我们要去斯波坎  -走吧
- We're going to Spokane. - Let's go.
我们跟道吉约在大堂
Meeting Dougie in the lobby.
姑娘们  咱们坐飞机兜风去
Girls, let's go for a plane ride.
不知道道吉有什么打算
Wonder what Dougie's up to now.
走吧
Let's go!
我有预感  一位名叫戈登·科尔的人会来电
I have a feeling a man named Gordon Cole will call here.
如果他打来  给他念这条信息
If he does, read him this message.
你非常优秀  布什内尔·穆林斯
You're a fine man, Bushnell Mullins.
我会铭记你的大恩大德
I will not soon forget your kindness and decency.
那联调局的人怎么办
What about the FBI?
我就是联调局的人
I am the FBI.
坐过去  我来开车
Move over. I'll drive.
-但道吉...  -珍妮·E  没事
- But, Dougie-- - Janey-E, it's okay.
这怎么回事  道吉
What's going on, Dougie?
系好安全带
Fasten your seat belt.
珍妮·E  银色野马赌场怎么走
Janey-E, how do we get to the Silver Mustang Casino?
你不会又要开始赌博了吧
You're not gonna start gambling again, are you?
我们要去见米彻姆兄弟
We're going to see the Mitchum brothers.
老爸开车
Dad can drive...
好厉害
really good.
未知号码
[笑脸]全部
我记得
I remember.
库柏
Oh, Coop.
我还记得
I remember.
希望这行得通
I hope this works.
正在发送...
请进  戴安
Come in, Diane.
你问我库柏前来找我那一晚的事
You asked me about the night that Cooper came to visit me.
我告诉你吧
Well, I'm gonna tell you.
想来一杯吗
You want a drink?
好
Yeah.
那是我和库柏失联...
It was three, maybe four years after, uh...
之后的三  四年
after I stopped hearing from Cooper.
当时我还在联调局工作
I was still working at the bureau.
某天夜晚
One night...
无人敲门
No knock...
门铃未响
No doorbell...
他就这么走了进来
...He just walked in.
我站在我的客厅
I was standing in my living room.
当时见到他我好开心
Oh, I was so happy to see him.
我紧紧拥抱他
I held him so close.
接着我们
And we, uh...
我们坐在沙发
We sat on my sofa.
开始聊天
Started talking.
我好想听他说说
I just wanted to hear everything
他去了哪些地方
about where he'd been and...
做了些什么
...what he'd been doing.
而他只想知道
He only wanted to know about, uh...
当时联调局的情况
what had been going on at the bureau.
我觉得他好像在拷问我
It felt like he was grilling me.
但我...
But I...
我告诉自己他只是
I told myself he was just...
他只是很想听听局里的新闻
He was just excited to hear about bureau news.
然后他靠过来
And then he leaned in.
他靠过来
He leaned in...
靠过来亲了我
Leaned in to kiss me.
我们只亲过一次
It only happened once before.
但是当...
But as soon as...
当他的嘴唇触碰到我的嘴唇
as soon as his lips touched mine...
感觉有点不对劲
...something went wrong.
我觉得很害怕
And I felt afraid.
他看到了我眼中的恐惧
And he saw the fear in me.
然后他笑了
And he smiled.
他笑了
He smiled.
然后他的脸
A-and his face...
然后就这么发生了
and that's when it started.
他强奸了我
He raped me.
后来
Afterward,
他带我去了一个地方
he took me somewhere.
他带我去了一个地方...
He took me somewhere like a...
好像是一个旧加油站
an old gas station.
旧...
Uh, old...
一个旧加油站
An old gas station.
未知号码
[笑脸]全部
我在警长办公室
I'm in the sheriff's station.
我把那些坐标都发给他了
I-I sent him those coordinates.
我在警长办公室
I'm in the sheriff's station...
因为...因为...
Because--because...
我不是我了
I'm not me.
我不是...
I-I'm not...
我不是我了
I'm not me.
我...我不是
I'm-I'm-I'm not.
我不是我了
I'm not me.
它们是真的
They're real.
这真的是幻人
That was a real tulpa.
警长办公室
Sheriff's station?
有人
造出一个你
我知道
I know.
操你的
Fuck you.
银色野马赌场
道吉
Dougie! Oh.
你看上去好极了  你看上去太好了
You look great. You look good.
我们都准备好了  飞机在等了
We're all set. The plane's standing by.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
伙计们  给我几分钟
Fellas, give me a moment.
珍妮·E  桑尼·吉姆  跟我来
Janey-E, Sonny Jim, come with me.
道吉说话有底气多了
You know, Dougie's talking with a lot of assurance.
也许和昏迷有什么关系
Maybe something to do with the coma?
副作用
Side effects.
我要离开一阵子
I have to go away for a while.
但我想告诉你们
But I want to tell you
我很喜欢和你们俩一起的时光
how much I've enjoyed spending time with both of you.
什么
What?
你们让我感到很快乐
You've made my heart so full.
你...你在说什么
What--what are you saying?
我们是一家人
We're a family.
道吉  我是说
Dougie--I mean...
我会回来的
I will be back.
你不是道吉
You're not Dougie?
什么
What?
不
No.
你是我爸爸
You're my dad.
我是你爸爸  桑尼·吉姆
I'm your dad, Sonny Jim.
我是你爸爸
I'm your dad,
我爱你
And I love you.
我爱你们俩
I love you both.
我要走了
I have to go.
我会尽快回来
You'll see me soon.
我会走进那扇红色的门
I'll walk through that red door,
永远地回家
and I'll be home for good.
别走
Don't go.
我必须要走
I have to.
不管你是谁
Whoever you are...
谢谢你
Thank you.
道吉  让我来理一理
Dougie, let me get this straight.
等等  等等  我也想听
Wait, wait, wait, I want to hear this, too.
坎迪  我的血腥玛丽呢
Candie, where's my bloody Mary?
好了
Okay.
你不卖保险
You don't sell insurance.
你是个联调局探员
You're an FBI agent...
失踪了25年
who's been missing for 25 years,
我们要带你取一个叫双峰镇的地方
and we need to get you to a town called Twin Peaks,
去警长办公室
to a sheriff's station.
道吉
Dougie...
我们爱你
We love you,
但是那种地方一般不欢迎我们
but we are not traditionally welcome at such places.
以及之前我们提到的那些...
Or by such aforementioned people--
执法部门的人
law enforcement types.
我很理解你们
I read you 100 percent.
朋友
Friends,
一切都要变了
that's about to change.
我很清楚
I am witness to the fact
你们俩都有一颗赤子之心
that you both have hearts of gold.
真的
They do.
他们真的有
They really do.
枪炮酒吧
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
酒吧隆重欢迎
the roadhouse is proud to welcome
爱德华·路易斯·西弗森
Edward Louis Severson.
两杯马丁尼
Two martinis.
谢谢
Thank you.
敬我们  奥黛丽
Here's to us, Audrey.
敬比利
Here's to Billy.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
奥黛丽献舞
Audrey's dance.
莫尼克
Monique!
莫尼克  那是我老婆  混蛋
Monique! That's my wife, asshole!
小心点
Careful!
查理  带我离开这里
Charlie. Get me out of here.
什么
What?